ACTWU's Out-of-Business Contracts 5619/035
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Out-of-Business Contracts
1937-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
Internatinal Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
Textile Workers Union of America
UNITE
5619/035
19.5 cubic feet
19.5 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of contracts from business that ceased operation. Includes contracts from Textile Workers' Union of America, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, and UNITE.
6826791
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
Novmeber 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America All other 5619 collections 5780/145: ILGWU. Association Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/146: ILGWU. Master Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/147: ILGWU. Independents. Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/158: ILGWU. Out-of-Business Contracts
Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing trade--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE) --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6826791
- Adams Scientific. Scott Laboratories. Local 1877., 1974-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Warwick, RI
- Allen Industries. Local 1372., 1955-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Compton, CA
- Anchor Woven Label. Local 1933B., 1981-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Alcoa, TN
- Anomatic. Local 1875., 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Westerville, OH
- Apollo Dyeing and Finishing. Local 1733., 1969-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Paterson, NJ
- BASF. Conductive Fiber Unit. Local 1526., 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Williamsburg, VA
- Boott Mills. Local 783T., 1945-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Lowell, MA
- Buckley and Mann. Brown's Beach Jacket. Local 580T., 1943-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Franklin, MA
- Canvil. Local 1797., 1970-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  English and French. Acton Vale, Quebec, Canada
- Cedar Riverside People's Center. Local 36., 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Minneapolis, MN
- Celion Carbon Fibers. BASF. Local 1781., 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Rock Hill, SC
- Chase Packaging. Local 194T. [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  St. Louis, MO
- Chase Packaging. Local 194T. [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Chase Packaging. Local 915T., 1949-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Vernon, CA
- Colgate Plastics. Local 1638., 1970-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Buffalo, NY
- Courtaulds Fibres Canada. Local 1779., 1965-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Cornwall, Ontario, Canada
- Courtaulds (Canada). Local 779. [folder 1 of 3], 1946-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Courtaulds (Canada). Local 779. [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Courtaulds (Canada). Local 779. [folder 3 of 3], 1980-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Curbell. Local 1748., 1967-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Douglas Randall Division. Walter Kidde and Company. Local 1766T., 1979-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Pawcatuck, CT
- Dou Temp. Local 1126., 1959-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Depew, NY
- Eagle Knitting Mills. Local 64., 1937-1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Milwaukee, WI
- Fabulous Formulas. Local 2465., 1984-1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Midland, Ontario, Canada
- Fleisher Finishing. Local 1913T., 1978-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Waterbury, CT
- Gold Star. Local 159T., 1941-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  North Kansas City, MO
- Gordon Campbell. Local 1484., 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada
- Jockey International. Local 2268. [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Kenosha, WI
- Jockey International. Local 2268. [folder 2 of 2], 1982-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kingston Spinners. Local 1881., 1973-1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Kingston, Ontario, Canada
- Lambeth Corporation. Local 1124., 1945-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  New Bedford, MA
- Leader Dyeing and Finishing. Local 1733. [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Leader Dyeing and Finishing. Local 1733. [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Lion Ribbon. Local 252., 1967-1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Secaucus, NJ
- Lion Ribbon. Local 252. Distribution Unit., 1965-1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Mail-Well Envelope. Local 1800., 1969-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Rochester, NY
- Mars Bluff Industries. Local 2506., 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Florence, SC
- Miller Bag. Star Specialty. Local 36., 1943-1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Morton Coatings. Local 1248T., 1947-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  East Providence, RI
- Neiman Brothers. Local 335., 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Chicago, IL
- Packaging Resources. Local 1805., 1970-1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Louisiana, MO
- Royal Mills. Local 252., 1956-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Formerly Royal Ribbon Mills. New York, NY
- Standard Lampshade. Local 7587., 1958-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Standard Shade. Local 7587., 1960-1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Stephen and Foster. Local 1495., 1960-1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Lockland, OH
- Stephen and Foster Bedding. Local 1495., 1981-1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Cincinnati, OH
- Synthane-Taylor Corporation. Local 1382., 1955-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  LaVerne, CA
- Three Printers. Old Deerfield Fabrics. Local 1733., 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Deerfield Fabrics. Cedar Grove, WS
- Toledo Mattress. Local 226-A., 1944-1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Toledo, OH
- True Temper Hardware. Local 1833., 1970-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Anderson, SC
- United Technologies Automotive. Local 1374. [folder 1 of 2], 1955-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Herrin, IL
- United Technologies Automotive. Local 1374. [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 140 Enterprises. Local 1733., 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 39 Minute Indian Village Cleaners. Local 124., 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Detroit, MI
- A & A Midwest Rebuilders Suppliers. Local 335T., 1977-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- A-1 Manufacturing. Local 2572., 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Louisville, AL
- Abe's Golden Needle. Local 333., 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Dearborn, MI
- Alperin. Local 137., 1982-1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Old Forge, PA
- Alperin Warehousing. Local 173, 1983-1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Adams Sponging and Company. Local 1., 1968-1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hyde Park, MA
- American Art Textile Printing. Local 1790. [folder 1 of 2], 1940-1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Brooklyn, NY
- American Art Textile Printing. Local 1790. [folder 2 of 2], 1974-1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- American Bennett. Local 146., 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  New Haven, IN
- American Guard-It Manufacturing. Local 4230., 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Amerima Ltd. Local 191., 1979-1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Youngstown, OH
- AMP-CEP. Local 9., 1985-1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Altoona, PA
- Amstar. Local 939T., 1947-1992 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Versailles, CT
- Analog Textile Processing. Local 2052., 1988-1993 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Union City, NJ
- Anderson Little. Local 1069., 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Angelica International. Local 211, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Weston, Ontario, Canada
- Aquascutum. Local 298., 1978-1992 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  English and French. Montreal, Quebec, Canada
- Arrow Linen Supply. Local 331., 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Asher. Local 309., 1937-1994 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Fitchburg, MA
- Aspen Imaging International. Local 2549., 1989-1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Lafayette, CO
- Athletic Helmet. Local 963., 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Knoxville, TN
- Atlantic Textile and Screen Printing. Screen Standard Makers and Printers. Local 1790. [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  New York, NY
- Atlantic Textile and Screen Printing. Screen Standard Makers and Printers. Local 1790. [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Atlas Sponging and Combining. Local 212., 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  Toronto, Ontario, Canada
- Atlas Sponging and Combining. Local 236., 1978-1992 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Babylon Burning. Local 42., 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  San Francisco, CA
- Bachrach Ltd. Local 23578A-T., 1981-1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Watertown, MA
- Bancroft Cap. Local 4H., 1966-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Farmingham, MA
- Bancroft. Local 25., 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Bardi Products. Local 1790., 1957-1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Barr. Local 55D., 1970-1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Los Angeles, CA
- Benay-Albee Novelty. Local 9., 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Newport News, VA
- Benkel Manufacturing. Local 2H., 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Botany "500". Local 75., 1968-1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Philadelphia, PA
- Botany "500". Local 746 and 746A., 1968-1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Northampton, PA
- Brady T-Shirt. Local 1088., 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  East Brady, PA
- Bridgeport Pants. Local 119D., 1963-1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Bridgeport, PA
- Brown Shoe. Local 176., 1990-1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Pocahontas, AR
- Brown Shoe. Multiple locals., 1978-1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Bucks County Housing Group. Local 2520., 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Langhorne, PA
- Cadillac Industries. Local 826., 1960-1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Mayaguez, PR
- Calvin Manufacturing. Local 2555., 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Tallapoosa, GA
- Cameo Curtains of New Bedford. Local 1129T., 1950-1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Canton Manufacturing. Local 485., 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Canton, IL
- Carhartt South. Local 2341., 1978-1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Drew, MS
- Cavalier Clothes. Local 25., 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Queens, NY
- Chemfab New York. Local 1906., 1989-1995 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Cheektowaga, NY
- Chris-Craft Industrial Products. Local 237., 1937-1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Waterford, NY
- Choctaw Manufacturing. Local 2395., 1981-1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Silas, AL
- Clappers of Roosevelt Field. Local 25., 1981-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Garden City, NY
- Clinton Swan Clothes. Local 4/190., 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Carlstadt, NJ
- Colucciello Tailored. Local 177., 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Fall River, MA
- Columbia Textile Services. Local 1733., 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Confection Bellemare Engineering. Local 2429., 1980-1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  English and French. Louiseville, Quebec, Canada
- County Laundry. Local 300., 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Mamaroneck, NY
- Crawford, a Carisbrook Company. Local 2422., 1986-1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Richmond, VA
- Crown Textile. Local 1111., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Talladega, AL
- Cupid Diaper Service. Local 331., 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Richmond Hill, NY
- Village Dye Works. Waverly Dyers. Local 1790., 1951-1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Custom Colors. Local 1970., 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Custom Drapery Cleaners. Local 124., 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Cyrus Stage. Local 187., 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Lawrence, MA
- D and L Clothing. Local 25., 1972-1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Astoria, NY
- D'Alonzo-Lancaster. Local 75/110., 1977-1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Delm., 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  French. Montreal, Quebec, Canada
- Depot Management. Local 215., 1987-1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Detroit Cover. Local 365., 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- DG Trim Products. Local 2536., 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Dover/Parkersburg. Local 1209T., 1946-1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Dover Fabrics. Local 1790., 1957-1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Yonkers, NY
- Downs Carpet. Local 80., 1961-1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Willow Grove, PA
- Dutron. Local 975., 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  South Bend, IN
- Dy-Dee Services. Local 124., 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Eagle Knitting Mills. Local 2203., 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Waupun, WI
- Eagle Pants and Suits. Local 25., 1978-1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Massapequa, NY
- Eastern Home Products. Local 2591., 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Elkhart, IN
- B. Ehrlich. Local 25/63., 1977-1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Les Enterprises L. S. (vetements)., 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Le Magasin de Vetement S. Farbstein., 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  French. Joliette, Quebec, Canada
- Favor-Eats. Local 9., 1985-1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  McConnellsburg, PA
- Felters. Local 232T., 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Millbury, MA
- First Union Management. Local 347., 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Morgantown, WV
- Florsheim Shoe. Local 51B., 1988-1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Flushing Shirt 3. Local 622., 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Paisley, PA
- Flushing Shirt Manufacturing. Local 622., 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Waynesburg, PA
- Fulton County Glove Manufacturing. Local 2486., 1961-1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Gloversville, NY
- Gentlemen's Wear House Factory Outlet. Local 1069., 1982-1994 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Globe International. Local 56A., 1992-1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Golden Belt Manufacturing. Local 248-A, 248-B, 248-C. [folder 1 of 2], 1939-1978 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  Durham, NC
- Golden Belt Manufacturing. Local 248-A, 248-B, 248-C. [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Golden Belt Manufacturing. Local 2533., 1988-1994 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  Randleman, NC
- Grossman Clothing. Local 25., 1971-1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  Roslyn, NY
- Grand Illusion Design. Local 2405A., 1990-1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  Schaumburg, IL
- G. S. G. Local 134., 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Guarantee Sponging. Local 236., 1980-1992 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Gurney Industries. Local 873., 1948-1987 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  Prattville, AL
- H. T. Industries. Local 169., 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  Hormigueros, PR
- B. W. Harris Manufacturing. Local 155., 1961-1996 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  St. Paul, MN
- Hawthorne Area Community Council. Local 36., 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Harvey Woods. Local 1300. [folder 1 of 2], 1953-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Woodstock, Ontario, Canada
- Harvey Woods. Local 1300. [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Hastings. Local 42J., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Herman's Sporting Goods. Local 654., 1992-1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Carteret, NJ
- Morris Hertling. Morrison Manufacturing. Local 25/63/4, 1977-1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Highland Yarn Mills. Local 319. [folder 1 of 3], 1937-1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  High Point, NC
- Highland Yarn Mills. Local 319. [folder 2 of 3], 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Highland Yarn Mills. Local 319. [folder 3 of 3], 1987-1997 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Hilton Manufacturing. Local 4/190., 1977-1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Linden, NJ
- Holley-Messmer. Local 388., 1988-1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- House of Maurizio. Local 162., 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Howard Avenue Apparel. Local 2295., 1976-1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Tampa, FL
- Hunter Mills. Local 215., 1956-1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Ian Michaels Shirtmakers. Local 2594., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Hialeah, FL
- Imperial Feather. Local 1169., 1986-1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Imperial Wear. Local 25., 1981-1987 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Impact Products. Local 2612., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  Lithonia, GA
- Importations Prevues. Local 2583., 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Intercontinental Branded Apparel. Local 694A., 1976-1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Interstate Foam Processors. Local 1932., 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- JPS Automotive Products. Local 2529., 1988-1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Port Huron, MI
- Jaco Manufacturing. Local 653., 1957-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Portage, PA
- Jain-Sax Industries. Local 25/63/4., 1977-1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Jayu Garment. Local 906., 1976-1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Clarksville, TN
- Johnson and Johnson. Chicopee Manufacturing. Local 630. [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Milltown, NJ
- Johnson and Johnson. Chicopee Manufacturing. Local 630. [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Johnson and Johnson. Chicopee Manufacturing. Local 630., 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Dayton, NJ
- Just Bottoms. Local 25/63/8/190., 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Staten Island, NY
- KCL Packaging of Canada. Local 986., 1966-1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Kittanning Apparel. Local 1088., 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Templeton, PA
- K Poster and Novelty. Local 1790., 1981-1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Kuppenheimer Factory Stores. Local 86., 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Canton, OH
- Kuppenheimer Manufacturing. Local 109. [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Wellston, OH
- Kuppenheimer Manufacturing. Local 109. [folder 2 of 2], 1991-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Walton Manufacturing. Kuppenheimer. Local 2490., 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Loganville, GA
- L and H Trousers. Local 25/63., 1977-1993 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Gasper La Fata and Company. Local 25/63., 1977-1993 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- L and S Leather Coats. Local 178., 1979-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Leon Siegler Industries. Local 1719., 1971-1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Leeftod. Bond's. California Joint Board., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- La Strada. Local 187., 1959-1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Lacy's Seven Mile. Local 124., 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Littler's. Local 71., 1984-1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Seattle, WA
- Londontown. Local 745., 1992-1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Eldersburg, MD
- Lewistown Speciality Yarns. Local 6., 1990-1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Lewistown, PA
- Lewistown Speciality Yarns. Local 1762., 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Lauren Danielle. Local 178., 1985-1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Liberty Coolidge Cleaners. Local 124., 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Linett Clothes. Local 4/158., 1977-1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Litchfield Garment. Local 155., 1980-1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Litchfield, MN
- Londontown. Local 745. Multiple locals., 1959-1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Louisiana Plastics. Local 2444., 1983-1995 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Panama City, FL
- Major Cleaners Enterprises. Local 279., 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Kearny, NJ
- Manhattan Industries. Local 910., 1965-1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Andalusia, AL
- Manhattan Industries. Multiple locals., 1969-1991 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Manhattan Industries. Local 226C., 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Americus, GA